Good evening. I want to read you something and, um, I want to read you something. I also
want to encourage you. I'm going to post a list of movies. People always laugh. People always
ask for a list of books. I know you're not reading the books. You can't, there's no time.
You don't, if you, unless you live in the city, you're not on a train. You're not reading the
books. I know that you ask for the books because it feels like the smart thing to do and I respect it,
but keep it a buck. You're not reading the books. I, um, I just, I mean, let's just keep it a thousand.
You're not reading the books, but I want to interest you in watching some films that I think
if you think I would be a great addition to the view, then you literally have no idea what I'm
about. Um, so if you would like to, I'm going to put a list of books. I mean, sorry, I'm going to
put a list of movies that I hope you'll engage in that can give you some real quick, um,
context, comprehensive context for the United States government. Okay. So like not this United
States government, the United States government, because a lot of people only think of things
within the context of their own mortality. However, the United States government has existed as long
as the United States has existed. And it's, you know, important to understand that context in order
to understand where we are, how we've been here before and what possibly could be next steps.
Um, so that's one, two, I want you to please try and look up, um, what's going on in Nepal.
It's incredible what's happening in Nepal. Uh, the real one, two, three of it is that there was, uh,
organizing effort by many Gen Zers in Nepal to protest. This was happening online. And once the
government got wind of it, they shut off the internet and when they shut off the internet,
they was like, Oh, for real? I organizing effects starting now. So they then decided to get in these
streets, Nepal NEPAL. They went in them streets. And when they got in the streets, the government
said, all right, since y'all want to act up, we're going to do a shoot to kill order. And they literally
ended up, uh, bringing, they shot 19 people. Uh, and that is when they said, Oh, we shooting people.
Okay. Okay. So then they started setting things on fire. And so they set the parliament on fire. Uh,
they also ran out the parliamentarians and the prime minister, the prime minister left his disabled wife
in his house in his burning house. And they actually, the, the young people went in and saved her and
took her to safety. Um, and they proceeded to chase the finance minister into the river, pulled him out
from the river. Uh, and therefore we think, okay, they done, they acting up like this is what it is
because riots are always seen as a reaction, a reaction of craziness. They're always presented
as some, um, sociopathic, you know, pathological behavior when ultimately riots are like Martin
Luther King, the voice of the unheard, but they also create scorched earth, right? They also can very
oftentimes be a, you know, fire is cleansing. Let's put it that way. Okay. Um, and so they,
they then got back on the internet on discord and the people for a new prime minister and this vote
for the prime minister was then legalized and they have a new prime minister and the new prime
minister is someone who came from the movement, the labor movement. It's, it's an elder. So, um,
someone's name is captain Jean-Luc Picard and gauge space, the final frontier. These are the voyages
of the starship enterprise. You know, my, my dog's name is Geordie Lafer on its continuing mission
to explore a strange new world, to seek out new life and new civilizations, to boldly go where no one
has gone before. You should also know that this was a gift given to me by Leonard. Leonard, uh, played
Molly's, uh, boyfriend, well, coworker, then boyfriend, then husband on insecure. And so he was
clean in his crib and he found this and he knew I would love it. So he gave it to me.
So for all you jackasses, I'd love to say, I don't have any friends on insecure.
If I didn't, my lips are so chap. I feel like they're peeling like an orange. Talk amongst yourselves.
Do not get another new phone. We are in the midst of what is continuously happening in the Congo.
And therefore we should not be advancing this. Stick with your old phone. I'll be right back.
I want to remind you that as everything is going on here in the United States,
the advancement of the devastation in Gessa continues.
We must remember that all of the actions of the United States are a party to colonialization,
colonization and imperialism. So whenever you are seeing what's going on, you know that there is
something else going on. And right now there is a large pause. Someone asked, what do our phones have
to do with Congo? So the technology of our phones runs with minerals. Everything that we have in this
world runs with minerals. Everything that we have in this world runs with some aspect of what we are
taking from this world. That's why there is renewable energy. And then there is unsustainable energy,
right? So like fossil fuels are non-renewable energies. They have a limited amount. And when
they're done, they're done, right? However, there are sustainable energies like wind, like water,
et cetera, that we should be deploying and implementing that end up being ignored because they don't make
the same amount of money. Because of course, scarcity is what drives price up. Cobalt is one of those
minerals. Cobalt is found in large quantities in the Congo. The Congo is probably, it's considered like
the richest mineral-based part of the world. It is home to ecosystems and deep, deep, deep concentrations
of really viable, valuable minerals that can make our whole world function. The concept of Africa is
that in effect, right? So like uranium, for instance, which ends up being a key component to not only like
nuclear weapons, but also to nuclear plants that power electricity. Yeah, they get that from
countries like Niger. And that's what's going on in, uh, France is that Niger said,
no more uranium, no soup for you. And, um, now they feel in some type of way. That being said,
uh, the, what, some of the ways in which people are trying to combat this is, you know, by battling the
capitalism with boycotting and by battling the, yes, chemo and the X, uh, cobalt is the real life
vibranium. Now there are other cobalt, um, I forgot the word for it. There's like other cobalt,
what's the word y'all? Don't call me Mandy. My name is Amanda. Um, what's the other word for cobalt?
What's like a cobalt, um, not sections, but there's other cobalt. Come on, where's my,
where's my geologists? There's other cobalt, um, what's the word? What's the word? Um,
no, like, no, like cobalt stores, like there's other cobalt, like mines, like there's other
cobalt clumps is not the word, but there's deposits. Ding, ding, ding, ding. Yes. So there
are large cobalt deposits in Greenland. Yeah. In the glaciers, as the glaciers have melted,
they have released, they have shown that there are other deposits, which I believe is also another
reason why these people don't give a gut damn about the climate change because they're literally
melting these mounting tops that are encased in the ice to reveal more opportunity for
mining, which is diabolical. So that's why we're not buying new phones. Okay. I wanted
to read you this. Um, well, they did try to go to Greenland and Greenland was like, get
the F out of here. Um, because I want us to continue to understand that we must continue
to center Ressa. We must continue to keep our eyes trained, our actions, um, and our attention
on Palestine and Ressa. Because if you look at the movies that I'm going to send for you
to watch, I'm going to post for you to watch, you understand, you begin to understand the cyclical
nature and that we are in just another cycle. We are just another version. We're another
part of the cycle. So we, we don't, we, we have to understand that indigenous people understand
that, but, uh, you know, those of us who are not, we, we fail, we oftentimes fail to do
so. Okay. Um, thank you to where God is Latina. So I wanted to read you this. Um, and I want
to take a moment to say this to you too, as we continue forward in what is of course, a
concerted effort to disrupt and to destroy any semblance of the rule of law and of the
rights, we will also have to stay sane. We will also have to stay sane. And so just as much as I
implore you to continue to increase your, uh, to increase your political education,
just as much as I implore you to increase your skills of community, right? And what you can bring
to your community, it is imperative that you also really ask yourself, what do I require?
What do I require? You know, a lot of us, we don't do that for many reasons. Sometimes, Claudia,
sometimes we don't do that because we feel like it's too selfish. Sometimes we feel like we don't
have time. Sometimes we just feel like it's not that important, but it is. So I want you to ask
yourself what you require. And I want you to remember that you are very privileged to be able
to provide yourself with what you require. And so you need to be doing that as long as you can.
Anyone who's in here and is going to challenge what I say as suggestions and, and positive positivity
with defeatist negative rhetoric, I will literally just block you. So I'm not interested in your point
of view that says that is anti what I'm saying. I am, it means absolutely nothing to me.
I do not care. If you feel like that's not a thing, then you go on your live and you talk to
your people about that. I am here to encourage and to empower. And those who receive it, it's here for
them. Those who can't yet, it's here for them. So keep that shit to yourself is basically what I'm
trying to say. So goddamn negative shit. All right. This is a letter that was posted by the homie
Rhonda Gerard by Dr. Ezedine Inghessa. So I want you to just sit with this and I want you to take
deep breaths while I'm reading it. Cause I want you to hear, and I really hope that you guys will
sit with it, listen to every word. And this is an empathy practice. Okay. So as I'm reading the words,
I want you to envision as I'm reading the words, I want you to put yourself there. If you feel yourself
getting emotional, I want you to take the ride. Um, but that's what we're, this is an empathy
practice and it's imperative that we get our empathy together because that's the thing that's
going to save us. I must write this down before the night devours me. My father's friend, a poet and
a guardian of words, the son of a family that owns the oldest library in Gessa, that sacred house where
history and imagination slept together like weary brothers. He is leaving. Yes. Leaving.
He is fleeing Gessa city. He wrote yesterday with the voice of a man who has reached the last edge of
human despair. I cannot take the books with me. If there is anyone who can save them, let him come.
It would break my heart to see them burn for I have placed my heart within them and my heart will burn
with them. This is not metaphor. This is not the polished language of Salons. He says plainly, my heart
will burn and I believe him. Dozens upon dozens of volumes, centuries of memory, law, history, economics,
literature, literature, the wisdom of the dead now lie waiting to be carried away like children from a
burning house. Not sold, not bartered, not traded, offered. Offered as one offers a soul to anyone
willing to save it from hell. This is Gessa. Where we are made to abandon again and again the last
sacred pieces of our existence. Not ornaments, not luxuries, but the very marrow of our being.
Here survival is surgery without anesthetic. We cut away memory to keep the breath.
We cut away words to keep the body. We cut away the past to stumble blind into a future that does not want us.
And so we go on, less and less human, until what is left is no man at all, but a wound
that breathes. Here in Gessa, books are exiled with their writers. Letters are orphaned like children
crying in the streets. Libraries, temples of memory are scattered like bones, like families fleeing in the
night. And I ask, what remains? What is left of us? A people stripped bare, stripped of houses,
of books, of the very act of remembering. A people ordered to forget. Are you listening?
A people ordered to forget. To forget. But no. No. Every page that burns becomes a prophet.
Every letter that turns to ash becomes a witness against heaven and earth. If the houses fall,
if the books burn, let it be known. This too is part of the crime. Not merely the killing of the body,
but the attempted erasure of memory itself. The murder of the soul. And yet even as the pages blacken,
they do not die. They rise. Yes, they rise as smoke into the night sky. Into the face of God himself,
whispering, we were here. We wrote. We dreamed. We loved. And I swear to you, if the world has any conscience
left, one day it will hear them. And it will tremble. And it will kneel. Now, because Instagram
is a dick, I can't see your comments. For some reason it has stopped loading your comments. So if you
are leaving comments right now, I can't see them. I wanted to read that to you because I wanted you
to hear what despair and resilience sound like. And that they are spoken with the same tongue.
It doesn't have to be one or the other. You don't have to make a choice between despair at what's going
on around you and fighting it. You can do both. And we have so many examples that have allowed us to
even be here. And I think some of us forget the miraculousness of our even existing. Do you know
how many things had to happen for you to be alive? I wish it was just that. I wish it just started that
fucking, but it doesn't. Cause those two people had to somehow find their way to each other. So as you
are thinking about your, your day, your weekend, your time, as you are thinking about your life,
your dreams, your frustrations, as you are considering your what next, know that there are people who are
currently in the midst of being exterminated, who are still able to see beyond their own despair and the
value of fighting till the end. Knowing that the end is mortality, but there is still so much more
living that goes on. And I know us Americans like to be real emotional, especially everyone's mindful
now. So everybody's real emotional. And I think that's a beautiful thing that we're getting in touch
with our emotions. I think it's a beautiful thing that we're getting in touch with our emotions,
but we're losing touch with what they mean. We're losing sight of the fact that you can't just have
the emotions. You got to understand them because if you don't understand your emotions, somebody else
will manipulate them. You can find that post at Rhonda Gerrard's page at R-A-J-A-R-R-A-R.
I wish you all a beautiful night. Take a moment to go outside and take a deep breath in.
And tomorrow morning, take a moment to go outside and take a deep breath in.
And in the meantime, in between time, let me also remind you that next week we have the
Amandaland Summit going down in New York City at the People's Forum. We would love for you to come
and support and support my work by also subscribing to my Patreon, which is $5 a month. Night, y'all.
Amandaland Summit going down in New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City at New York City.